

Yurii Kitsera

Contacts

Address

Ukraine, Lviv

Phone

+380678656486

Email

y.kitsera@gmail.com

Linkedin

yuriy-kitsera-2a896b115

github

github.com/YraKot

Professional Summary

1.5+ year experience as a Front-End dev. I am interested in React and I'm using it in my pet project. Looking for a job that will help me improve my skills. Responsible, diligent, reliable, able to listen, friendly, able to learn quickly and team player.

Work Experience

Chunkup, Web Development Lab, front-end dev.

04.2019 - now

- Commercial Client product (library/plugin)
- https://qa.k12buy.com/landing/
- https://qa.prorfx.com

UPQODE LLC, front-end dev.

01.2018 - 04.2019

- www.accenture.com
- www.digitank.com
- www.iup.com
- https://dragonboat.io/
- https://zinc.co
- www.skil-tools.com
- www.ego.com
- www.chase.com

Freelance web developer

06.2017 - 09.2017

- www.proditech.com.ua
- www.ecobot.com.ua

Lviv Polytechnic National University, Institute of Computer Sciences and Information Technologies, Department of Applied Linguistics, Position: engineer.

09.2013 - 12.2017

Additional Education

EPAM Systems, The Education program: "Data Warehouse Business Intelligence".

09.2016 - 01.2017

Education

Lviv Polytechnic National University, Institute of Computer Technologies, Automation and Metrology, Specialist degree in Computer System Engineering.

2006 - 2011

Languages

Ukrainian – native

English – intermediate

Russian - intermediate

Technical skills

- HTML5, PUG, Nunjucks
- CSS3, SCSS, SASS, LESS
- JS, ES6, TS, jQuery
- React JS basic
- Gulp, Webpack, Git
- Photoshop, Zeplin, Sketch